ILR School Alumni Scrapbooks /4120
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Alumni Scrapbooks
1967-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4120
1 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Scrapbooks.
7994658
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 10, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4078: ILR School 40th Anniversary Documents /4118 MB: ILR School Alumni Memorabilia /4119m: ILR School Richard Jacobstein Memorabilia
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Alumni Association
7994658
- ILR Reunion Scrapbook 1940's, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ILR Reunion Scrapbook 1950's, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ILR Reunion Scrapbook 1960's, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ILR Reunion Scrapbook 1970's, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR Reunion Scrapbook 1980's, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILR Reunion Scrapbook 1990's, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ILR Reunion Scrapbook 2000's, 2000-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Homecoming, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Photographs (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Reunion Schedule, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cornell ILR School Stickers (Box 1, Folder 11A)
- Cornell ILR School Banner (Box 1, Folder 11B)
- ILR-Reunion Scrapbook Information Sheets, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Scope and Contents
  Questionnaires sent out to Alumni
- ILR-Reunion Scrapbook Information Sheets, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ILR-Reunion Scrapbook Information Sheets, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ILR-Reunion Scrapbook Information Sheets, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15A)
- ILR-Reunion Scrapbook Information Sheets, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15B)
  12 photographs and several negatives